<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Travel on Hanna</title>
    <link>/travel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Travel on Hanna</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zn-Hans</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2015 20:29:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/travel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Kauai, Hawai&#39;i</title>
      <link>/travel/kauai_hawaii/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 21:17:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/kauai_hawaii/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to return to Hawai’i this summer, but I specifically wanted to avoid Oahu and the tourist-developed atmosphere. Because of the volcano eruption on the Island of Hawai’i, and a lack of hostels that suited my needs in Maui, I decided on Kauai. This island has a completely different feel from Oahu; it’s more laid back, has a down-to-earth vibe, and is teeming with authentic culture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zion National Park, Utah</title>
      <link>/travel/zionnationalpark_utah/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 21:17:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/zionnationalpark_utah/</guid>
      <description>Zion National Park had been at the top of my list for years and I finally made it there on a school spring break trip with a group of awesome randos. Zion exceeded all of my expectations, including how cold it is in March. This trip inspired me to make a goal to see as many National Parks as possible in my lifetime!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banff, Alberta CA</title>
      <link>/travel/banff_albertaca/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 21:17:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/banff_albertaca/</guid>
      <description>One day I saw a picture of Banff and I thought it was really beautiful, so I googled whether there were any hostels in Banff, and if they have a public transit system. Both were a yes and the trip was born in under 10 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salt Lake City, Utah</title>
      <link>/travel/saltlakecity_utah/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 21:17:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/saltlakecity_utah/</guid>
      <description>Salt Lake City was the final stop on what turned into the 2017 #summerofviews, and it did not disappoint. This city has a lively downtown area and quick access to outdoor adventure on every level, not to mention great public transit and a solid foodie scene - something for everybody!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oahu, Hawai&#39;i</title>
      <link>/travel/oahuhawaii/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 21:17:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/oahuhawaii/</guid>
      <description>The trip that started them all. I had zero intentions of traveling to Hawaii. My goal was to get to Canada for a fishing trip, but after my flights fell a part I wasn’t going to be able to make it in time to meet up with my family to catch my ride to Canada.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>